{
    "subject": "resource/Pooja_Sharma",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/India",
    "human_readable": "Pooja Sharma was born in India.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9205989241600037,
            "question": "Where was Pooja Sharma born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.870334267616272,
            "question": "Is Pooja Sharma Indian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8194661736488342,
            "question": "What country is associated with Pooja Sharma's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44459566473960876,
            "question": "Does Pooja Sharma have any siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43367066979408264,
            "question": "What is Pooja Sharma's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38994377851486206,
            "question": "Where might Pooja Sharma currently reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3361984193325043,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Pooja Sharma?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.334334135055542,
            "question": "Is there any notable event associated with Pooja Sharma's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3248276114463806,
            "question": "What are some of Pooja Sharma's interests?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27748051285743713,
            "question": "What languages does Pooja Sharma speak?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pooja Sharma was born in India.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8351_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Pooja Sharma's interests?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8351_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any notable event associated with Pooja Sharma's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8351_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Pooja Sharma?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8351_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8351_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8351_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8351_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8351_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8351_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8351_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8351_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8351_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8351_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8351_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all the documents mention Pooja Sharma being an Indian actress and model, which implies that she was born in India. The specific birthdate (12 February, 1989) and city (Delhi) mentioned in some of the documents further support this conclusion."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Pooja Sharma was born on 12 February, 1989, in Delhi, India. Therefore, the statement \"Pooja Sharma was born in India\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}